[
    {
        "question": "The Mandarin lives in:",
        "choice1": "The Valley of Spirits",
        "choice2": "The Mountains of Asgard",
        "choice3": "The Canyons of Atlantis",
        "choice4": "The Cave of Souls",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Dr. Doom was expelled from college because?",
        "choice1": "He killed a teacher",
        "choice2": "He got into a fist fight with Reed Richard",
        "choice3": "He caused an explosion with an experiment",
        "choice4": "He was cheating to get good grades",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Weasel has worked closely with?",
        "choice1": "Cable",
        "choice2": "Deadpool",
        "choice3": "Captain America",
        "choice4": "Iron Man",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Ms. Marvel (Carol Danvers) has never been known as?",
        "choice1": "Captain Marvel",
        "choice2": "Rogue",
        "choice3": "Warbird",
        "choice4": "Binary",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The Thing has how many fingers on both hands, including his thumbs?",
        "choice1": "8",
        "choice2": "6",
        "choice3": "10",
        "choice4": "4",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Fin Fang Foom is an alien from?",
        "choice1": "Krypton",
        "choice2": "Maklu IV",
        "choice3": "Mars",
        "choice4": "Vulcan",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Who paid Mac Gargan to become the Scorpion?",
        "choice1": "Felicia Hardy",
        "choice2": "The Kingpin",
        "choice3": "Norman Osborn",
        "choice4": "J. Jonah Jameson",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Captain America was frozen in which war?",
        "choice1": "World War I",
        "choice2": "World War II",
        "choice3": "Cold War",
        "choice4": "American Civil War",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Thor has two war goats to pull his chariot. They are named?",
        "choice1": "Balder and Hermod",
        "choice2": "Thunder and Lightning",
        "choice3": "Ask and Embla",
        "choice4": "Toothgrinder and Toothgnasher",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the K in MODOK stand for?",
        "choice1": "Knowledge",
        "choice2": "Killing",
        "choice3": "Kyle",
        "choice4": "Karate",
        "answer": 2
    }
]